gogoinflight.com 2018-03-08

# Gogo Privacy Policy

### GOGO PRIVACY AND COOKIE POLICY

**Last updated 2020/01/01**

**Summary**

**In this section we summarize some of the key provisions of the full Privacy and Cookie Policy, which starts under the "General" heading below. In the event of a conflict between this summary and the full Policy, the full Policy will control.**

**This policy is for users of our services. If you are a prospective, current, or former employee, please see the privacy notice on our careers page.**

**What information we collect.** We collect information about you when you use the Gogo services. This information includes registration details, personal identifiers and your service preferences. We also collect information automatically about the device from which you access the service, and use cookies to collect information on website usage and access. To find out more about Cookies and how to alter or remove your Cookie settings, visit www.allaboutcookies.org. We may supplement the information we collect with information from external parties, for example if you link to us from a social media platform.

**How we use this information.** We use the information collected to operate and develop our services and to improve personalized content based on your preferences including advertisements, features and service performance.

**Who we share your information with.** We may share your information with roaming partners, airline partners and external parties who store and process your information on our behalf. These include group companies who provide services to us in several countries and who follow this Privacy and Cookie Policy.

Gogo and selected external parties may send you information on products and services that may be of interest to you when permitted by applicable law. If you prefer not to receive targeted advertising you can opt out by following the unsubscribe instructions provided in the promotional email or by contacting us directly at [customercare@gogoair.com](mailto:customercare@gogoair.com) (US; Canada), [uksupport@gogoair.com](mailto:uksupport@gogoair.com) (UK), [support@gogoair.com.mx](mailto:support@gogoair.com.mx) (Mexico), support@gogoair.com.br (Brazil) or [support@gogoair.co.jp](mailto:support@gogoair.co.jp) (Japan).

**How we protect your information.** The service connection is protected by an encrypted link. However, we cannot provide an encrypted communication channel between the Wi-Fi point and your device following access. Gogo recommends the use of secure virtual private network protocols and disabling file-sharing to increase your security.

**General**

Gogo LLC and its subsidiaries and affiliates, ("Gogo," "us" or "we") respect your concerns about privacy and value our relationship with you. This Privacy and Cookie Policy is intended to inform you of the types of information we collect, as well as our policies and practices regarding the collection, use and disclosure of that information through the web pages, tracking devices, interactive features, mobile applications, blogs and their respective contents at Gogo’s on-ground and in-flight URLs, including among others www.gogoair.com, gogoair.com/jp and custhelp.gogoinflight.com (collectively, "Gogo Domains"), in addition to our Twitter, Facebook and other social networking sites, and their respective contents (collectively, the "Sites"), and the Gogo services (collectively with the Sites, the "Services"), whether accessed via computer, mobile device or other technology.

Click on one of the links below to jump to the listed section:

QUICK GUIDE TO CONTENTS

  1. Information Collected through our Services
  2. How We Use the Information Collected
  3. Information We Share
  4. Information We Receive from External Parties
  5. Consent to Processing and Transfer of Information
  6. Your Access and Choices
  7. Advertising; How to Opt-out
  8. Links to Other Sites
  9. How We Protect Personal Information
  10. Children
  11. How to Contact Us
  12. Compliance with the EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)
  13. Updates to Our Privacy and Cookie Policy

### 1\. Information Collected through our Services

The airlines on whose planes the Services are available do not collect any information through your use of the Services, but we may share certain types of information with such airlines, as described below. Please remember that this Privacy and Cookie Policy only covers your activities while on the Gogo Domains; to the extent you visit external party websites, including the websites of our airline partners, the privacy policies of those websites will govern. Users who reside outside of the United States should note that their information will be held and processed in the United States. In certain circumstances, foreign courts, law enforcement agencies or regulatory agencies may be entitled to access your personal information without notice to you. By accepting this Privacy Policy, whether by establishing an Account (as defined below), signing-in to your Account, accessing the Services as a guest, or otherwise using the Services, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing.

**Personal Information You Provide to Us**   
When using the Services, you will, in most cases, be required to provide information that could reasonably be used to contact you, or to identify you personally, or that otherwise relates to your person (such as your name, mailing or billing address, telephone number, or email address, email preferences, password for your Account and password hint question, and a complete set of credit card information that enables us to receive your payment (including your credit card authorization number) (collectively, "Personal Information")). For example, Gogo may collect Personal Information when you register on the Sites, purchase Services, request information, submit comments or participate in some promotion, survey or other feature of the Sites, or otherwise communicate or interact with us. In addition, you may choose to provide contact information for friends you may wish us to contact. When you provide us information for these "refer a friend" messages, we use the information only to send the message you request and the information will not be used for other marketing purposes unless your friend consents. You may be identified to the friend in connection with such message. Please check that friends you refer are happy for us to contact them. The Sites may also ask you to provide other information about yourself, such as demographic information (gender, zip code, age, etc.) or certain information about your preferences, product use and interests.

**Information Collected by Automated Means**   
Whenever you use the Services, Gogo, as well as any of our external-party advertisers and/or service providers, may use a variety of tools and technologies that automatically or passively collect information about how the Services are accessed and used ("Usage Information"). Usage Information may include, among other things, browser type, operating system, the page served, the time, the type of content being transmitted (e.g., video content) or application being used, how many users visited the Sites, origin and destination information, flight information, subscriber status and preceding page views. This data helps us to manage our network and provides us with information about the use of the Services, such as how many visitors visit a specific page on the Sites, how long they stay on that page, and which hyperlinks, if any, they "click" on. This information helps us to keep the Services fresh and interesting to our visitors and to tailor content to a visitor’s interests. Usage Information is generally non-identifying, but if Gogo associates it with you as a specific and identifiable person, Gogo treats it as Personal Information. Gogo also collects your network traffic information, including information sent to or received from the websites you visit. We will not use this network traffic information for any purpose other than to administer the Services, such as to maintain and secure our network and to help you with Service-related questions, or as may be required by law or by law enforcement officers acting under the color of law.

**Device Identifiers**   
In the course of collecting Usage Information, Gogo also automatically collects your IP address, MAC Address or other unique identifier ("Device Identifier") for the computer, mobile device, Wi-Fi card, technology or other device (collectively, "Device") you use to access the Services. A Device Identifier is a number that is automatically assigned to your Device when you access a website or its servers, and our computers identify your Device by its Device Identifier. When you visit the Sites, we may view your Device Identifier. We use this information to determine the physical location of your Device, including origin, destination, flight route information, and longitude and latitude information. We also may use this information to enhance the Services and we may associate your Device Identifier with your Personal Information. The technologies used on the Services to collect Usage Information, including Device Identifiers, may include, without limitation:

**Cookies**   
Cookies are data files placed on a Device when it is used to visit the Sites or access the Services ("Cookies"). For example, we may use Cookies to collect and store certain information about your Account or to facilitate your use of the Service as a guest. We may use both session Cookies (which expire once you close your web browser) and persistent Cookies (which stay on your computer until you delete them). The types, use and duration of the Cookies used are as follows:

Type of Cookies | Purpose of Use | Duration  
---|---|---  
Session Cookies | Session Cookies ensure that you are recognized when you move from page to page within the Sites and that any information you have entered is remembered. For example, session Cookies ensure that items placed in a shopping basket don’t disappear by the time you reach the checkout. You can choose not to accept session Cookies by changing the settings in your browser. | Session Cookies expire once you close your web browser.  
Persistent Cookies | 

Persistent Cookies help the Sites remember your information and settings when you visit them in the future. This results in faster and more convenient access.

Features of the Service made possible by persistent Cookies include: authentication, language selection, theme selection, menu preferences, internal site bookmarks or favorites, among others. Cookies may enhance your online experience by saving your preferences while you are visiting a particular Site.

Persistent Cookies also allow us to select which of our advertisements or offers are most likely to appeal to you and display them while you are using the Services.

We currently use a external party ad network to serve Cookies in the United States; and we may partner with external party ad networks to serve our Cookies in the European Union, Canada and other jurisdictions.

| Eternal, unless deleted by the user.  
  
If you have any browser windows or tabs open to one of our inflight Sites when our inflight connectivity Services system shuts down on a flight, and one or more of those windows or tabs remain open when you regain internet access on the ground, those windows or tabs will reload with Gogo's on-ground Site, a site separate from our inflight Site(s), _which also uses Cookies in accordance with this Privacy and Cookie Policy_.

If you would prefer not to accept Cookies, most browsers will allow you to: (i) change your browser settings to notify you when you receive a Cookie, at which time you can choose whether or not to accept it; (ii) disable existing Cookies; or (iii) set your browser to automatically reject any Cookies. Start with these sites to learn more about your browser’s privacy controls:

• Internet Explorer

• Firefox

• Chrome

• Safari

• Opera

Additionally, Firefox and Chrome have extensive repositories of add-ons that can help enhance your control over your privacy.

You can also learn more about Cookies by visiting www.allaboutcookies.org, which includes additional useful information on Cookies and how to block Cookies using different types of browsers. For more information on advertising using Cookies and how to opt-out of advertising Cookies specifically, please see Advertising; How To Opt-out below.

Please be aware that if you disable or reject Cookies, some features and Services may not work properly. For example, if you disable or reject Cookies, we may not be able to recognize and associate you with your purchase, whether using your Gogo Account or Guest Access.

**Web Beacons**   
We may also include web beacons (also known as Internet tags, pixel tags, tracking beacons and clear GIFs) with the content and ads that we deliver to you, which we will use to collect information regarding your interaction with such content and ads. A web beacon is a transparent graphic image placed on a web page or in an email, which indicates that a page or email has been viewed or that an email has been forwarded. In addition, a web beacon allows external parties to obtain information such as the IP address of the computer that downloaded the page on which the beacon appears, the URL of the page on which the beacon appears, the time the page containing the beacon was viewed, the type of browser used to view the page, and the information in Cookies set by external parties. A web beacon may also tell your browser to get content from another server.

back to top

### 2\. How We Use the Information Collected

We use and store information we collect about and from you to: provide the Services to you, respond to requests that you make, manage our network, improve the Services, and better tailor content, advertisements, offers and the features, performance and support of the Services; and for purposes disclosed at the time you provide your Personal Information or otherwise with your consent. We may use records of your e-chat sessions with our representatives for support, training and improvements to our Services. If you provide feedback to us, we may use and disclose such feedback for any purpose, provided we do not associate such feedback with your Personal Information. If you submit a request to us concerning your Personal Information, we will use you’re the information we have to help verify your identity before we can compete your request. Similarly, we use such data to fulfil any orders or requests that you make to us in the course of our business with you.

We may use your Personal Information for marketing and to send you advertising materials, electronic newsletters, or promotional emails about our products and services. You can opt-out of receiving further promotional messages from us by following the unsubscribe instructions provided in the promotional email you receive or by contacting us directly at [customercare@gogoair.com](mailto:customercare@gogoair.com) (US; Canada), [uksupport@gogoair.com](mailto:uksupport@gogoair.com) (UK), [support@gogoair.com.mx](mailto:support@gogoair.com.mx) (Mexico), [support@gogoair.com.br](mailto:support@gogoair.com.br) (Brazil) or [support@gogoair.co.jp](mailto:support@gogoair.co.jp) (Japan). We may also use your Personal Information to send you Service-related communications.

We will use your Personal Information to ensure system security and anti-fraud systems are working and to prevent and contain any such issues.

To the extent that certain information that we collect in providing Gogo’s inflight connectivity services constitutes customer proprietary network information (" **CPNI** "), Gogo complies with applicable law governing CPNI.

back to top

### 3\. Information We Share

Except as otherwise stated in this Privacy and Cookie Policy, we do not trade, rent, or share your Personal Information with external parties, unless you ask or authorize us to do so. We may share non-Personal Information, such as aggregate user statistics, demographic information and Usage Information with external parties. We may also share your information as disclosed at the time you provide your information, as set forth in this Privacy and Cookie Policy and in the following circumstances:

**Roaming Partners**. Gogo has agreements in place with various companies (typically hotspot aggregators or telecommunications companies) **("Roaming Partners"** ) that provide the Services to their customers **("Roaming Partner Users"** ). If you are a Roaming Partner User, we may send to the applicable Roaming Partner: (a) the userID and password you submit to us when you sign in to use the Services in order to authenticate you and for security purposes; and (b) information regarding the times that you started and stopped use of the Services and bandwidth used.

**Airline Partners**. In order to provide the Services efficiently and carry out your requests, we may also disclose Personal Information, such as your email address, Device Identifier, and Usage Information to the airline partner on whose plane you have accessed the Services.

**External Parties Providing Services On Our Behalf**. In order to provide the Services, carry out your requests, make various features, services and materials available to you through the Services and respond to your inquiries, we may share your Personal Information or Usage Information with external parties that perform functions on our behalf, such as (a) companies or individuals that: host or operate our Sites; analyze data; provide customer service; or manage payments; (b) advertisers; and (c) sponsors or other external parties that participate in or administer our promotions or provide marketing or promotional assistance. In such cases, such external parties are not entitled to use this information for any other purpose.

**Your Agreement to Have Your Personal Information Shared**. While using the Services, you may have the opportunity to opt-in to receive information and/or marketing offers from someone else or to otherwise consent to the sharing of your information with an external party, including companies who advertise their services via the Service. If you agree to have your Personal Information shared, your Personal Information will be disclosed to the external party and the Personal Information you disclose will be subject to the privacy policy and business practices of that external party.

**Affiliates**. To facilitate our marketing and communications efforts, we may share some or all of your Personal Information with our Affiliates ("Affiliates" are parent companies, subsidiaries, joint ventures, or other companies under a common control), in which case we will require our Affiliates to honor this Privacy and Cookie Policy. If you are a resident of California, Brazil or Mexico, you may ask us to refrain from sharing your information (whether collected online or offline) among our Affiliates for their marketing purposes, if the Affiliates are separate legal entities. Please tell us your preference by contacting us as indicated in the "How to Contact Us" section of this Privacy and Cookie Policy. We will comply with the applicable data privacy laws and direct marketing requirements in the relevant jurisdictions and may seek opt-in or opt-out consents as appropriate for the collection, use and transfer of personal information in accordance with the laws in the relevant jurisdictions.

**Business Transfers**. If our company or our assets related to this Privacy and Cookie Policy are acquired by another company, your Personal Information, and any other information that we have collected about the users of the Services, may be disclosed to that company as part of the due diligence process and will be transferred to that company as one of the transferred assets. Should such a sale or transfer occur, we will use reasonable efforts to direct the transferee to use information you have provided through the Sites in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy and Cookie Policy. Also, if any bankruptcy or reorganization proceeding is brought by or against us, all such information may be considered an asset of ours and as such may be sold or transferred to external parties.

**Law Enforcement Compliance**. We may be required by law, or by law enforcement officers acting under the color of law, to record some or all of your communications on or through the Services. We may, and you hereby authorize us to, disclose your Personal Information (including your Account Information, if applicable) and other information including your communications through the Services, if required by applicable law or by law enforcement officers acting under the color of applicable law, or if we believe in good faith that such disclosure is necessary to: (a) comply with relevant laws or to respond to subpoenas or warrants served on us; or (b) protect or defend the rights, property, or safety of Gogo, you, other users, or external parties (especially in emergency situations).

**Governmental Authorities**. Some governmental authorities may require that we share your Personal Information with them (e.g., for sales on Gol, we may be required to share your Personal Information and transaction/purchase details with the applicable Brazilian tax authority). We may, and you hereby authorize us to, disclose your Personal Information to applicable governmental authorities to the extent required by applicable law.

back to top

### 4\. Information We Receive from External Parties

Gogo may receive information about you from external parties. For example, if you are on another website and you opt-in to receive information from Gogo, that website will forward to us your email address and other information about you so that we may contact you as requested. You may also choose to participate in an external party application or feature (such as one of our Facebook or Twitter applications or a similar application or feature on a external party website) through which you allow us to collect and share (or the external party to collect and share) information about you, including Personal Information. In addition, we may receive information about you if other users of an external party web site give us access to their profiles and you are one of their "connections" or information about you is otherwise accessible through your "connections" web page, profile page or similar page on a social networking or other external party website or interactive service.

We may also supplement the information we collect about you through the Services with other information from external parties in order to enhance our ability to serve you, to tailor our content to you and to offer you opportunities to purchase products or services that we believe may be of interest to you. Using multiple data sources, we derive your airline, tail number, origin, destination and flight number of the flight when you access the Services. We may combine the information we receive from these external parties with information we collect through the Services. In those cases, we will apply this Privacy and Cookie Policy to any Personal Information received, unless we have disclosed otherwise.

We may match the information we receive about you from external parties with the information we collect from you ourselves in order to enhance your experience with the Services and to select which of our advertisements or offers are most likely to appeal to you and display them while you are using the Services.

back to top

### 5\. Consent to Processing and Transfer of Information

By using the Services, you agree to the terms of this Privacy and Cookie Policy and you expressly consent to the processing of your Personal Information according to this Privacy and Cookie Policy.

If you are a User who resides outside the United States, please be aware that information we collect will be transferred to and processed in the United States. By using the Services, or providing us with any information, you consent to the collection, processing, maintenance and transfer of such information in and to the United States and other applicable countries in which the privacy laws may not be as comprehensive as or equivalent to, those in the country where you reside and/or are a citizen. Gogo takes steps to provide an adequate level of privacy protection for Personal Information it receives in the United States from the European Union and Switzerland.

European Union or Swiss citizens with inquiries or complaints regarding this Privacy and Cookie Policy should contact Gogo at:

Gogo LLC

Attn: General Counsel

111 N. Canal Street, Suite 1500

Chicago, IL 60606

Brazilian citizens with inquiries or complaints regarding this Privacy and Cookie Policy should contact Gogo at [support@gogoair.com.br](mailto:support@gogoair.com.br) (Brazil). Mexican citizens with inquiries or complaints regarding this Privacy and Cookie Policy should contact Gogo at [support@gogoair.com.mx](mailto:support@gogoair.com.mx) (Mexico).

back to top

### 6\. Your Access and Choices

We offer you choices regarding the collection, use, and sharing of your Personal Information. When you receive promotional communications from us, you may indicate a preference to stop receiving further promotional communications from us and you will have the opportunity to "opt-out" by following the unsubscribe instructions provided in the promotional email you receive or by contacting us directly at [customercare@gogoair.com](mailto:customercare@gogoair.com) (US; Canada), [uksupport@gogoair.com](mailto:uksupport@gogoair.com) (UK), [support@gogoair.com.mx](mailto:support@gogoair.com.mx) (Mexico), [support@gogoair.com.br](mailto:support@gogoair.com.br) (Brazil)or [support@gogoair.co.jp](mailto:support@gogoair.co.jp) (Japan). Gogo does not charge for this opt-out service, and your opt-out request will be processed within 30 days of the date on which we receive it. For Canadian and Brazilian residents, your opt-out request will be processed within 10 days of the date on which we receive it. For Mexican residents, your opt-out request will be processed within 20 days of the date on which we receive it.

Regardless of your indicated email preferences, we may send you administrative emails regarding the Services, including, for example, purchase confirmation, account creation confirmation, and notices of updates to our Terms of Use Agreement or Privacy and Cookie Policy.

#### You have the right to: 

  * Access and be informed – to request, to know what personal information we collect, use, and disclose about you, including the right to know the specific pieces of personal information we have collected about you
  * Portability – to request a portable copy of your personal information
  * Delete – to request that we delete personal information that we have about you, subject to certain exceptions allowed under applicable law. You can also delete your profile by simply deleting all the data fields, which will cause our server to delete the information from its online form
  * Not Sell – to opt out of the sale of your personal information to external parties (but note that we DO NOT sell personal information to external parties)
  * Object – to object to the processing of your personal information (but note that this right has limitations so we may provide our services to you)

We will not discriminate against you because you exercised any of these rights.

If you wish to verify, correct, update or delete any of the Personal Information provided to us, you may do so by editing it in your Account page, if applicable, or by contacting us at the above email address. For questions about the collection of Personal Data by Gogo, or to exercise the right to access, correct, update, or delete such data or object, for legitimate purposes, to the processing of Personal Data for which Gogo is the data controller, as provided under applicable law, please click here. You may also call our customer service line at 1-877-350-0038 (USA) or check our website for the international number. You may also reach our team by SMS text or via our customer chat tool.

We will take reasonable steps to verify your identity prior to responding to your requests. The verification steps will vary depending on the sensitivity of the personal information and whether you have an account with us.

If you wish to withdraw or modify your consent to our collection, use or disclosure of the Personal Information provided to us, we reserve the right to terminate your Account or your continued use the Services if the withdrawal or modification of your consent would or could adversely affect our operations or the Services.

There may be cases where restrictions on the amount of data that can be disclosed to data subjects under applicable law (for example, if that would necessarily involve disclosing data about another person). Gogo is permitted to withhold some types of Personal Data in certain circumstances, subject to applicable local law requirements. If there is a dispute, please contact the Gogo privacy officer at [privacyofficer@gogoair.com](mailto:privacyofficer@gogoair.com). In addition, data subjects have the right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority. If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact our U.S.-based external party dispute resolution provider (free of charge) at https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request.

We may engage in programs with our airline partners and their advertising partners for certain promotional programs, such as free session passes. Any such program will be clearly marked and will require your consent to share any personal information before you may engage with the promotion.

If you are a Mexican or a Brazilian resident and wish to limit the use or transfer of any of the Personal Information provided to us, you may contact us at the above email addresses. Please note that unless you state otherwise, we may send any corrected or updated Personal Information to every organization to which your Personal Information has been disclosed in accordance with this Privacy and Cookie Policy. In accordance with our routine record keeping, we may delete certain records that contain Personal Information you have submitted through the Services. Please note that we may be required (by applicable law or otherwise) to keep this information and not delete it (or to keep this information for a certain time, in which case we will comply with your deletion request only after we have fulfilled such requirements). You should be aware that it is not always possible to completely remove or delete all of your information from our databases without some residual data remaining in our archives because of backups and other reasons.

If you are a Mexican resident, your request to verify, correct, update, delete or limit the use or transfer of any of the Personal Information provided to us, will be processed within 20 days of the date on which we receive it.

You may designate an authorized agent to make a request under the CCPA on your behalf. When submitting the request, please ensure the authorized agent identifies themselves as an authorized agent.

#### Right to Withdraw Consent

You may withdraw your consent at any time; however, Gogo will not be able to provide or continue to provide Services or marketing communications to you.

back to top

### 7\. Advertising; How to Opt-out

Gogo licenses technology to serve advertisements on its own Sites and within its content as that content is served across the Internet. In addition, Gogo may use external party analytics vendors to evaluate and provide us with information about the use of the Services and viewing of our content. We do not share Personal Information with these external parties, but ad network providers, the advertisers, the sponsors, and/or analytics service providers may set and access their own Cookies, pixel tags and similar technologies on your Device and they may otherwise collect or have access to information about you, including Usage Information. We and our network advertisers may target advertisements for products and services in which you might be interested based on your use of the Services, visits to the Sites and other websites. We may use a variety of companies to serve advertisements.

If you prefer to not receive targeted advertising, you can opt-out of some network advertising programs that use your information. To do so please visit the Digital Advertising Alliance (DAA) Opt-Out Page: http://www.aboutads.info/choices. European users can also go to http://www.youronlinechoices.com. Please note that even if you choose to remove your information (opt-out), you will still see advertisements while you’re browsing online. Additionally, many network advertising programs allow you to view and manage the interest categories they have compiled from your online browsing activities. These interest categories help determine the types of targeted advertisements you may receive. The DAA Opt-Out Page provides a tool that identifies its member companies that have Cookies on your browser and provides links to those companies.

back to top

### 8\. Links to Other Sites

Our provision of links to other websites or locations is for your convenience and does not signify our endorsement of such other websites or location or its contents. We have no control over, do not review and cannot be responsible for these outside websites or their content. These other websites may send their own Cookies to your Device, may independently collect data or solicit Personal Information and may or may not have their own privacy policies. Please be aware that the terms of our Privacy and Cookie Policy do not apply to these outside websites. You should independently assess the authenticity of any website which appears to be or claims that it is one of our Sites (including those linked to through an email or social networking page).

back to top

### 9\. How We Protect Personal Information

The connection through which you access the Services is an SSL-encrypted link. However, following such initial access, due to multiple users of our inflight Wi-Fi access point, Gogo does not provide an encrypted communication channel, such as Wired Equivalent Privacy (WEP), or Wi-Fi Protected Access (WPA2), between our in-flight Wi-Fi access point and your Device. Gogo’s inflight internet connectivity service generally supports secure Virtual Private Network (VPN) and Secure Shell (SSH) access. If you have VPN, Gogo recommends that you use secure VPN protocols for greater security. Subject to the network management and limitations provisions discussed in our terms of use for the inflight internet connectivity service (accessible inflight at https://buy.gogoinflight.com/upp/terms.do and on the ground at http://www.gogoair.com/terms), SSL-encrypted websites or pages, typically indicated by "https" in the address field and a "lock" icon, can also generally be accessed through the inflight internet connectivity service. You should be aware, however, that data packets from un-encrypted Wi-Fi connections can be captured by technically advanced means when they are transmitted between a user’s Device and the Wi-Fi access point. You should therefore take precautions to lower your security risks. Gogo recommends that you follow good security practices, such as ensuring that file-sharing is not enabled while accessing the Internet from an un-encrypted public network and that laptops have a personal firewall and other protections against malware. Gogo recommends that sensitive or private information should not be accessed via or transmitted over an un-encrypted connection. While Gogo takes reasonable steps to protect your security, please be aware that we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and you use the Services and provide us with your information at your own risk.

back to top

### 10\. Children

We do not intentionally gather Personal Information about Users who are under the age of 16. If we become aware that we have unknowingly collected Personal Information from a child under the age of 16, we will make reasonable efforts to delete such information from our records.

back to top

### 11\. How to Contact Us

Should you have any questions, concerns or complaints regarding this Privacy and Cookie Policy, please contact us at [customercare@gogoair.com](mailto:customercare@gogoair.com) (US; Canada); [uksupport@gogoair.com](mailto:uksupport@gogoair.com) (UK), [support@gogoair.com.mx](mailto:support@gogoair.com.mx) (Mexico), [support@gogoair.com.br](mailto:support@gogoair.com.br) (Brazil) or [support@gogoair.co.jp](mailto:support@gogoair.co.jp) (Japan).

**Notice to Canadian, Brazilian and Mexican Residents - Access to Personal Information / Contact Information**

We are accountable for all Personal Information in our custody and control and have designated a Privacy Officer who is ultimately accountable for the handling of all Personal Information in our custody and/or control, and for ensuring that the principles described in this Privacy and Cookie Policy are being complied with.

If you have any questions about the accuracy of information that we have collected about you, you can have access to that information in order to verify and update it, unless we are permitted or required under applicable laws to refuse your access to such information. You may write or email our Privacy Officer at the address below to request access to Personal Information that we have about you or to obtain further information about our privacy policies or practices:

Gogo - Privacy Office

Attn: Legal Department

111 N. Canal Street, Suite 1500

Chicago, IL 60606

Email: [privacyofficer@gogoair.com](mailto:privacyofficer@gogoair.com)

back to top

### 12\. Compliance with the EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)

In addition to the notice provided above, the following notice applies to EU data subjects. In the event there is a conflict between the two as it applies to EU data subjects, this section shall take precedence. For purposes of this Section 12, the term “ **Personal Data** ” shall have the meaning given by Regulation (EU) 2016/679.

#### The Types of Personal Data That We Collect

  * **Personal Data that you provide to us**. Name, mailing or billing address, telephone number, or email address, email preferences, password for your Account and password hint question, and a complete set of credit card data that enables us to receive your payment (including your credit card authorization number).
  * **Personal Data collected by automated means**. Usage information may include, among other things, browser type, operating system, the page served, the time, the type of content being transmitted (e.g., video content) or application being used, how many users visited the Sites, origin and destination data, flight data, subscriber status, preceding page views, and network traffic information.
  * **Device identifiers**. IP address, MAC Address or other unique identifier for the computer, mobile device, Wi-Fi card, technology or other device you use to access the Services.
  * **Cookies**. We may use both session Cookies (which expire once you close your web browser) and persistent Cookies (which stay on your computer until you delete them). 
  * **Web beacons**. Includes the IP address of the computer that downloaded the page on which the beacon appears, the URL of the page on which the beacon appears, the time the page containing the beacon was viewed, the type of browser used to view the page, and the data in Cookies set by external parties.
  * **Personal Data from external parties**. Using multiple data sources, we derive your airline, tail number, origin, destination and flight number of the flight when you access the Services. If you choose to opt in, non-Gogo websites will forward your contact data and external party applications/sites (such as Facebook and Twitter) will share your personal data with us. We may also obtain data about you from persons you are connected to on social media sites.

#### Purposes for the Processing of Personal Data; Legal Basis

We process your Personal Data on the following legal bases, and for the following purposes:

  * for entering into and performing the contract between you and Gogo (to provide the Services and process payment information);
  * for our legitimate business interests (to provide the Services to you, respond to requests that you make, manage our network and business, provide training and support, improve the Services, and better tailor content, advertisements, offers and the features, performance and support of the Services)
  * as regards the use of cookies and other similar technologies, based on your consent and/or opt-out mechanisms as required by Directive 2002/58/EC and any successor legislation;
  * for purposes disclosed at the time you provide your Personal Data or otherwise with your consent;
  * to comply with our legal obligations.

We do not use your Personal Data for any automated decision making covered by Articles 22(1) and (4) of Regulation (EU) 2016/679.

Gogo may retain your Personal Data both during and after the time you are our customer, but we won’t keep it longer than needed. The amount of time we keep it depends on the type of Personal Data and the purpose for processing. For example, we may need it for regulatory compliance, to maintain our internal financial or transactional records, to communicate with you about our relationship, or in cooperation with law enforcement agency requests.

#### Recipients of Personal Data

  * **Roaming Partners**. Gogo has agreements in place with various companies (typically hotspot aggregators or telecommunications companies) (“Roaming Partners”) that provide the Services to their customers (“Roaming Partner Users”). If you are a Roaming Partner User, we may send to the applicable Roaming Partner: (a) the userID and password you submit to us when you sign in to use the Services in order to authenticate you and for security purposes; and (b) data regarding the times that you started and stopped use of the Services and bandwidth used.
  * **Airline Partners**. In order to provide the Services efficiently, carry out your requests, and provide you with offers and advertisements tailored to your interests, we may also disclose personal data, such as your email address, Device Identifier, and Usage Information to the airline partner on whose plane you have accessed the Services.
  * **External Parties Providing Services On Our Behalf**. In order to provide the Services, carry out your requests, make various features, services and materials available to you through the Services and respond to your inquiries, we may share your Personal Data or Usage Information with external parties that perform functions on our behalf, such as (a) companies or individuals that: host or operate our Sites; analyze data; provide customer service; or manage payments; (b) advertisers; and (c) sponsors or other external parties that participate in or administer our promotions or provide marketing or promotional assistance. In such cases, such external parties are not entitled to use this data for any other purpose.

#### Transfer of Personal Data to an External Country; Appropriate Safeguards

Personal Data collected by Gogo may be stored or processed in the United States or in any other country where Gogo or its affiliates, subsidiaries, or external party service providers maintain facilities. EU data subjects who provide Personal Data to Gogo acknowledge the processing and transfer of that data to the United States and around the world. Gogo will execute agreements with external parties for the transfer of personal data outside of the EU. These agreements may use European Commission-approved Standard Contract Clauses and/or employ additional or alternative appropriate safeguards.

### 13\. Compliance with the California Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA)

In addition to the notice provided above, the following notice applies to California residents.

We have collected the following personal information from our users over the past 12 months. What information we collect varies depending on how you interact with us and our services.

  * We collect personal identifiers, including your real name, your Gogo username, your IP address, your MAC address, and other unique identifiers from your device. If you call our customer service team, then we will also collect your phone number. For processing your payment, we only collect a credit or debit card token (usually the last 4 digits), your name and billing address, as necessary.
  * In your use of the services, we collect commercial information around what you buy from us, to meet our legal, financial, and customer service obligations. As a telecommunication provider, we collect your browsing history (limited only to the hosting sites and not the complete browsing story) for our billing purposes. We collect this information when you use our inflight services. If you interact with the Gogo sites, we collect information about the interaction with the sites as to improve your experience. If you call into our customer service team, we may also collect contact and account information, such as your phone number or email address, to ensure we can communicate with you and complete your given request.
  * _How do we use the personal information we collect?_ We use the above-referenced categories of personal information for our business and commercial purposes as further described in Section 2 of this Privacy Policy.
  * _What categories of sources do we collect your personal information from?_ We collect the above-referenced categories of personal information directly from you, automatically from your devices, from our service providers who perform business functions on our behalf, your friends who refer you to us, our airline partners, and social media, as further described in Section 1 of this Privacy Policy.
  * _What categories of other parties do we share your personal information with?_ We disclose the above-referenced categories of personal information to our affiliates, service providers, business and advertising partners, airline partners, advertising networks, data analytics providers, and social networks, as further described in Section 3 of this Privacy Policy.
  * We do not sell the personal information of California residents and we have not engaged in any sales in the last 12 months.

### 14\. Updates to Our Privacy and Cookie Policy

This Privacy and Cookie Policy and other information on the Sites may be updated periodically and without prior notice to you, and any changes will be effective immediately upon the posting of the revised Privacy and Cookie Policy on the Sites. However, we will use your Personal Information in a manner consistent with the Privacy and Cookie Policy in effect at the time you submitted the information, unless you consent to the new or revised notice. We will post a prominent notice on the Sites to notify you of any significant changes to our Privacy and Cookie Policy and indicate at the top of the notice when it was most recently updated.

back to top
